Guide to the Yale Club of New Haven Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Club of New Haven records
1909-1996
RU 266
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2
(7 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, minutes, financial records and statements, and mailing samples documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Club of New Haven.
Yale Club of New Haven
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 8-C-2 (YRG 8-C-2), Records of Yale regional alumni organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, minutes, financial records and statements, and mailing samples documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Club of New Haven.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale Club of New Haven; Yale University -- Alumnae and alumnae -- Societies, etc.
- Records, 1909-1960; Accession 1961-A-007
  - Correspondence, 1914-1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of Meetings, 1909-1960 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
- Records, 1949-1982; Accession 1983-A-113
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2018.
  - Financial Statements, 1949-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Former Directors, 1965-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mailing Samples, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Material
    - 1964-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Records
    - 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Whitlock, Reverdy, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Records, 1951-1974, 1983; Accession 1984-A-075
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2019.
  - Minutes of directors' meetings, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes
    - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mailing samples
    - 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1974, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence on by-laws, 1951-1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - By-laws and amendments, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Article, "The First Fifty Years of the Yale Club of New Haven" from the "Journal of The New Haven Colony Historical Society", vol. 41, no. 2, Spring 1995; Accession 1995-A-058
  - Article, "The First Fifty Years of the Yale Club of New Haven" from the "Journal of The New Haven Colony Historical Society", vol. 41, no. 2, Spring 1995 (Box 1)
- Invocations of Yale Club of New Haven meetings, and newletter, Vol. I, no. 1, 1992-1996; Accession 1997-A-045
  - Invocations of Yale Club of New Haven meetings, and newsletter, Vol. I, no. 1, 1992-1996 (Box 1)